<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>/</id>
  <title>CTP Ethiopia News</title>
  <subtitle><![CDATA[Updates by CTP's communications.]]></subtitle>
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
  <updated>2021-07-07T00:56:44+02:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>CTP Ethiopia News</name>
    <uri>/</uri>
  </author>
  <entry xml:lang="en">
    <id>/blog/application-update/</id>
    <title>Application Update</title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Hi Everyone!\
Decisions are out! If you haven't already, please check your emails as soon as possible. This year, we received a large number of applications to Level 2 from extremely qualified candidates. But unfortunately, we had a limited number of spots for our level 2 section and could not accept everyone who applied. So if you applied to Level 2 but received an email saying that you've been accepted to Level 1, it means that we were not able to accept you to Level 2.</p>]]>
    </content>
    <link href="/blog/application-update/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
    <published>2021-07-07T00:56:44+02:00</published>
    <updated>2021-07-07T00:56:44+02:00</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry xml:lang="en">
    <id>/blog/announcing-ctp-ethiopia-2021-summer-session/</id>
    <title>Announcing CTP Ethiopia 2021 Summer Session</title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h2 id="due-to-numerous-requests-we-have-received-we-have-decided-to-extend-the-application-deadline-until-monday-june-29-11-59-pm-est-you-will-be-notified-of-your-application-status-in-early-july-sessions-will-start-on-july-5th-thank-you-to-those-of-you-who-applied-and-we-look-forward-to-reading-the-rest-of-your-applications"><strong>Due to numerous requests we have received, we have decided to extend the application deadline until Monday, June 29, 11:59 pm EST. You will be notified of your application status in early July. Sessions will start on July 5th. Thank you to those of you who applied and we look forward to reading the rest of your applications!</strong></h2>
<h3 id="application-description">Application Description</h3>
<p>Welcome to CTP Ethiopia’s 2021 Summer Sessions Application. As the COVID-19 outbreak develops, we are doing everything we can to hold our regular summer sessions while keeping our CTP students and instructors safe. Hence, in light of the public health advice, and travel restrictions this year’s session will take place virtually. Once accepted, attendance to the summer session is completely <strong>FREE</strong>! Our team is working really hard to make these new virtual sessions as fruitful and worthwhile as our traditional in-person sessions. We have limited space so make sure to complete this application as soon as possible. To be considered for the summer sessions, you have to complete this application in its entirety.</p>
<p><a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSc70z3YatsKz3ifPWNmUEocIlncjIGrZPX2dtLPh5a-dRPxHg/viewform">APPLY</a></p>]]>
    </content>
    <link href="/blog/announcing-ctp-ethiopia-2021-summer-session/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
    <published>2021-06-05T00:51:32+02:00</published>
    <updated>2021-06-05T00:51:32+02:00</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry xml:lang="en">
    <id>/blog/ctp-alumni-whereabouts/</id>
    <title>CTP Alumni Whereabouts</title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Now that most of the early and regular decisions are out, we wanted to highlight some of our CTP Alumni who have been accepted to prestigious colleges abroad this year.</p>
<p>Aimen Ali — Dartmouth College\
Akotet Yeshaw — KAIST\
Beemnet Andualem — NYU Abu Dhabi\
Dagim Haddis — Columbia University &amp; Tufts University\
Efrata Thewidros — Lafayette College\
Hawi Humnessa — Cornell University\
Kidest Frew — Cornell University\
Keto Etefa — Pomona College\
Nebus Adane — MIT\
Tsigemariam Yizengaw — Columbia University\
Wakuma Tesfaye — Columbia University\
Yeabsira Tofik — Harvard University</p>
<p>Congratulations to you all! We are so proud of you! All of your efforts and passion have paid off. The hard work is not over.</p>
<p>Let the passion, goals, and hard work continue and we can’t wait to see you do monumental things.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>To learn more about CTP and what we do, visit this <a href="https://ctpethiopia.org/about">page</a> and we would like to invite you to <a href="https://ctpethiopia.org/donate">contribute</a> what you can to help us reach more students.</p>
</blockquote>]]>
    </content>
    <link href="/blog/ctp-alumni-whereabouts/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
    <published>2021-04-22T00:47:19+02:00</published>
    <updated>2021-04-22T00:47:19+02:00</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry xml:lang="en">
    <id>/blog/spring-sessions-update/</id>
    <title>Spring Sessions Update</title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Good Morning, </p>
<p>\
CTP would like to thank all of you that attended the first day of Spring Sessions today! We hope you have learned one or two things about the college applications process. But wait! We are not done yet! We will have the second and final day of our Spring Sessions event today starting from 5:00 PM. In today’s session, you will be given the chance to ask questions about college applications and whatnot. Make sure to show up later if you have questions you want to ask the CTP Team or want to hear what the CTP team has to say about the different facets of the college application process during the Q&amp;A. We can’t wait to see y'all there!</p>
<p>P.S. You can find the zoom link for the Spring Sessions event on the poster that has been shared via all of our social media platforms or you can <a href="http://tinyurl.com/ctp2021spring">click here</a>.</p>]]>
    </content>
    <link href="/blog/spring-sessions-update/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
    <published>2021-04-04T00:58:16+02:00</published>
    <updated>2021-04-04T00:58:16+02:00</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry xml:lang="en">
    <id>/blog/spring-sessions-2021/</id>
    <title>Spring Sessions 2021</title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h2 id="spring-sessions-are-back">Spring Sessions are back!</h2>
<p>We are pleased to announce that CTP will be holding its annual Spring Sessions event this weekend over Zoom, and you are all invited! We will discuss everything about the College Application Process. We will talk about the Common Application, Standardized Tests, Financial Aid, Essays, and a whole lot more.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Nothing is off-limits!</p>
</blockquote>
<p>You will get to hear about the experiences of students that navigated the college application process and made it to the other side. You will also have the chance to get all of your questions answered during the Q&amp;A. You can find more information about the Spring Sessions event on the poster below. We hope to see you there!</p>
<p>Join us on zoom: <a href="https://tinyurl.com/ctp2021spring">tinyurl.com/ctp2021spring</a></p>]]>
    </content>
    <link href="/blog/spring-sessions-2021/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
    <published>2021-04-01T00:29:58+02:00</published>
    <updated>2021-04-01T00:29:58+02:00</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry xml:lang="en">
    <id>/about/</id>
    <title>About</title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h2 id="ctp-ethiopia-news">CTP Ethiopia News</h2>
<p>CTP Ethiopia News is the official communication portal of <a href="https://ctpethiopia.org">CTP Ethiopia Inc.</a> We post important updates, program announcements, and information here. To learn more about CTP, visit the <a href="https://ctpethiopia.org/about">following page</a>.</p>]]>
    </content>
    <link href="/about/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
    <published>2019-07-09T02:00:00+02:00</published>
    <updated>2019-07-09T02:00:00+02:00</updated>
  </entry>
</feed>
